Ah, I'm in.
あ、入っちゃった
Look.
ほら
My feet are so stiff.
足こきなわね
Toes.
足指
It was amazing, so many people came.
なんかすごい、人いっぱい来たね
Well then, I'm going to sit down and go play right away.
じゃあちょっと、おなにしてあらすぐ遊戯行きまーす
I'm already asleep.
もうなんか寝てるよ
Because earlier...
だってさっきの...
Wait a minute, post?
ちょっと待って、ポストへ?
Have you never been to the post?
ポスト行ったことない?
Yeah.
うん
For now, I'd like to continue from earlier.
とりあえずさっきの続きしたいね
I went in.
入っちゃった
I want to quickly continue what I said earlier,
ちょっとさっきの続き早くしたいから、
I'm coming.
行ってくるね
I'll donate money.
寄料行きます
Sorry to those who got cut off in the middle earlier.
さっき途中で切れちゃった人すいません
I went in.
入っちゃった
Look.
ほら
I guess I'll wipe the salt off a little and then play daddy.
ちょっと一回塩拭いたらパパをしようかじゃあ
I wiped off a lot of salt.
めっちゃ塩拭いちゃった
I
私
It will cover you again.
また 被ってくれるわけです
Please take a screenshot.
どうぞ、スクショ
Take a screenshot quickly.
早くスクショして
Hurry up because my hands are getting tired.
もう手疲れるから早くして
I'd rather have a meal than be so bored.
もうこんなにクパしてるより私、おなにしたいんですけど
Look closer.
近 くで見て
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I'll clean up a bit once.
一回ちょっと片付くわ
The sheets are soaking wet.
びしょびしょのシートをね
hang on.
待って
Thank you for waiting.
お待たせしました
Is it strange again?
またおかしい?
Is there something wrong with the window?
窓おかしいの?
copper?
どう?
Does it look okay?
大丈夫そう?
Ah, I can't see you're healed.
あ、治ったって見ねてる
good.
よかった
sorry.
ごめんなさい
OK
No, I thought shaking it would probably cure it, so I tried shaking it.
いや、なんか、振ったら治るかなと思って振ってみた
Healed.
治った
thank you.
ありがとう
What should I do?
何しようかな?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I want to do more, Minami.
もっとしたいよ、南はね
Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマス
It's kind of difficult to be at the top, after all.
上位ってなんかむずいじゃん、だって
I did the top one too.
上位もやったけど
Very difficult and tiring.
非常に難しくて疲れる
Has the alien update started?
宇宙人の更新始まった?
Is something going on again?
また何かやらなってる?
Alien update.
宇宙人の更新
It opens a lot.
めっちゃ開ける
Yes, door up.
はい、ドアアップ
It's par.
パ ーだよ
Do you want to eat as a side dish?
おかずにされてご飯する?
I'm doing it because I want to.
するからやってるんだよ
I won't do it if you don't.
しなかったらやらないよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It won't stop.
止まらないよ
It doesn't stop.
止まらない
I want grandpa.
おじいちゃん欲しいよ
Sleep.
寝て
Can you help me more?
助けますか、もっと?
Is it more strange?
もっとおかしい?
I really like grandpa.
一体おじいちゃん好きだよ
Looks like I can wait.
待ちできそう、それな
It feels like the waiters are being wiped out.
待ち人殲滅って感じだわ
Wait a minute, I'll clean it up once and for all.
ちょっと待って、片付けするね、一回
I can't really move.
ちょっとまじ動けないわ
help me.
助けて
That's right, if I were on SNS or something.
そうだ ね、もし私がSNSとかやってたらね
I still want that as a gift,
まだ 欲しいものギフトに あれをね、
I'll definitely order a bucket seat.
ケットシート頼むね、間違いなく
It seems like it can be done in no time.
手間ですぐ行けそうだよね
I agree.
そうだね
I want you to go.
行かせて欲しいわ
Won't you come out again?
もう出ない?
I might still come out if I try hard.
まだ出るかも頑張れば
The escape neck is a little small.
逃げちくびがちょっと小さい
Which one?
どっち?
This way?
こっち?
Let's get it out, hey.
出そうぜ、イエーイ
Stand up and look at me all over.
立って全身見てて
Bai Zi.
白姿
About this?
このこと?
Can I wipe the tide with this?
これで潮拭き、いけるかな?
Ah, it feels good.
あー、気持ちいい
It feels good but it's tiring.
気持ちいいんだけど疲れる
This one fits better.
こっちの方がしっくり来るわ
Your breasts are beautiful.
おっぱいきれいですね
How many cups?
何カップですか?
It's a nice cup.
いいカップだよ
What is Manguri?
まんぐりって何?
Would you like it closer?
もっと近くがいい?
It made me even happier.
もっと嬉しされた